{
    "subject": "resource/Lorraine_Toussaint",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Trinidad",
    "human_readable": "Lorraine Toussaint was born in Trinidad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9412451386451721,
            "question": "Is Lorraine Toussaint from Trinidad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9069834351539612,
            "question": "Where was Lorraine Toussaint born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7670314908027649,
            "question": "What is Lorraine Toussaint's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089352607727051,
            "question": "What country is associated with Lorraine Toussaint's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6805616617202759,
            "question": "What nationality is Lorraine Toussaint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6219455003738403,
            "question": "How might Lorraine Toussaint's upbringing in Trinidad have influenced her acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.400979220867157,
            "question": "Where did Lorraine Toussaint spend her early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31048014760017395,
            "question": "Is Trinidad the birthplace of any famous actresses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2942582964897156,
            "question": "Can you name an actress born in Trinidad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09193283319473267,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Trinidad who are not actors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lorraine Toussaint was born in Trinidad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8366_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name an actress born in Trinidad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8366_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Trinidad the birthplace of any famous actresses?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8366_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Lorraine Toussaint spend her early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8366_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8366_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is my evaluation:\n\n* Document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8366/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt states that \"Actress Lorraine Toussaint was born and reared in Trinidad & Tobago\".\n* Document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8366/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt states that \"Lorraine Toussaint is a Trinidadian-American actress and producer.\"\n* The other documents do not provide information that contradicts the birthplace of Lorraine Toussaint.\n\nTherefore, my evaluation is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Lorraine Toussaint was born in Trinidad, West Indies Federation (as mentioned in the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8366/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt). Therefore, the statement \"Lorraine Toussaint was born in Trinidad\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}